instafilez.com 2009-04-09

# Privacy Policy

INFORMATION Instafilez.com GATHERS AND TRACKS 

Instafilez.com gathers two types of information about users:

  * Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions like registration, to receive our electronic newsletters, to participate in our message boards or forums, to email a friend, and from participation in polls and surveys.
  * Information Instafilez.com gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our site. Our web server(s) log IP address and visitor's domain name. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about the visitor. This information maybe be used for purposes such as examining traffic and to investigate misuse or abuse of any aspect of this site. This information is stored in a protected area of the site's logs and may be shared at Instafilez discretion with appropriate law-enforcement bodies or in good faith with other third parties. We do not collect and evaluate this information for specific individuals. Our Web servers do not automatically record e-mail addresses of the visitors. 

Instafilez.com Gathers User Information In The Following Processes:

Optional Voluntary Information  
We offer the following services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users:

1\. E-mail notifications  
We will send out notifications about payments and other activity related to your account. You might also receive periodic notifications about the changes in features for as long as you a registered member of Instafilez.com. 

2\. Electronic newsletters (Dispatches)  
We will offer a electronic newsletter to users. Instafilez.com gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management page. Users can also subscribe to the newsletters at the time of registration.

3\. Message boards/forums  
Users of the site’s Message Boards and Forums must register separately for these services (both are free of charge) in order to post messages, although they needn't register to visit the site. During registration the user is required to supply a username, password, and email address.

4\. “E-mail this to a friend" Service  
Our site users can choose to electronically forward a link, page, or documents to someone else by clicking “e-mail this to a friend”. The user must provide their email address, as well as that of the recipient. This information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the email. The information is not used for any other purpose.

5\. Polling  
We may offer interactive polls to users so they can easily share their opinions with other users and see what our audience thinks about important issues. Opinions or other responses to polls are aggregated and are not identifiable to any particular user. Instafilez.com may use a system to "tag" users after they have voted, so they can vote only once on a particular question. This tag is not correlated with information about individual users.

6\. Surveys  
Instafilez.com may occasionally conduct user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our sponsors, advertisers and partners.   
Children  
Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.  
Usage tracking  
Instafilez.com tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. Instafilez.com does break down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser).  
Instafilez.com sometimes tracks and catalogs the search terms that users enter in our Search function, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.

USE OF INFORMATION  
Instafilez.com uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.  
As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters and to enable users to participate in polls, surveys, message boards, and forums. We send out newsletters to subscribers on a regular schedule (depending on the newsletter), and occasionally send out special editions when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing. When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We track search terms entered in Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don't track which terms a particular user enters.  
Instafilez.com creates aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers, sponsors and partners. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs. Because we don't track the usage patterns of individual users, an advertiser or sponsor will never know that a specific user clicked their ad. We will not disclose any information about any individual user except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

SHARING OF THE INFORMATION  
Instafilez.com uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience's demographics.

OPT-OUT POLICY  
We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:  
· Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our users 

YOUR CONSENT   
By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Instafilez.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

COOKIES  
Some elements of our site may send your computer a Cookie. A Cookie is a very small file which computers use to store information about websites and vice-versa.

Third party Cookies motioned above are not personally identifiable - that is to say, they do not allow third party advertisers to gain significant personal information about who you are.

Cookies may be used to identify trends in a user's browsing pattern. Information gathered from visitors' visits to this and/or other sites may be used to determine which advertisements are served on this and/or other sites.

Visitors may choose not to allow Cookies to be served to their computers as a way of "opting out" of such anonymous identification. Visitors should investigate the functionality of their Internet browser which disallows Cookies. We do not provide technical support for such activities.

Forum members may be served an additional Cookie which allows their browser to verify their identity at each visit without the user having to manually log in.

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

REGISTRATION  
Optional registration for site promotions, newsletters, member access areas and the Forums may request additional personal information about a user. This information is stored in a protected area of the site's database and may be shared at Instafilez discretion with appropriate law-enforcement bodies or in good faith with other third parties. 

SECURITY AND TERMS OF USE  
This site has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

By using our site you consent to the collection and use of information as specified in this policy. Should we decide to alter our Privacy Policy, this page will be updated to reflect those changes in order to keep our visitors in the know.
